Won't leave
떠나려면
Without a dropkick on her
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
자자스 자자스 나사타나다 자자스
-She summoned me, the evil god -Evil god
- 저 애가 소환한 난 악마다 - 악마다!
-I gotta kill her or else -What?
저 애를 죽이지 않으면 뭐?
-I can't go back to hell -Sister...
지옥에 갈 수가 없어 자매여...
Yeah, yeah, yeah Life next to death, I combat with my chainsaw
그래! 그래! 그래! 죽음과 살기 위해, 전기톱으로 싸워야지!
If you go too far
네가 막 나가면
I'll slice you up completely
널 완전히 썰어버릴 거야!
Your halo Must get it back
네 후광을 반드시 되찾아야지!
-Never miss a chance -Hey, seriously?
기회를 절대 놓치지 마 정말 그럴 거야?
-To attack her from behind -You're so mean
뒤에서 공격하려고? 넌 못됐어
I'll never give up
난 절대 포기 안 해
Yurine, you're off your guard!
유리네, 방심하고 있군!
Now! Time to finish you with the Royal Copenhagen!
지금이다! 로열코펜하겐으로 끝내주지!
Huh? What? I missed...
어, 뭐지? 실패다...
Can't leave Earth
지구를 떠나려면
Without a dropkick on her
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
But until then
하지만 그때까진
-Let's all have fun together -Yeah!
모두 같이 놀자! 신난다!
JULY 9TH 17:00
'7월 9일 오후 5시'
LIFE THEATER
'인생극장'
The Goddess of Victory smiles upon me.
승리의 여신이 내게 미소짓는다
JULY 9TH 17:24
'7월 9일 오후 5시 24분'
Lost big time, yet again.
또 왕창 잃었다
I should've resisted the urge!
지르지 말아야 했어
What the hell was I thinking?
대체 무슨 생각을 한 거야?
How could I go completely broke in just 30 minutes?
어떻게 겨우 30분 만에 완전히 빈털터리가 됐지?
This alley is dangerous.
이 골목은 위험하지만
I only took this shortcut so I wouldn't miss the sale!
세일 시간에 맞추려고 이 지름길로 왔어
But my right hand insisted that I play the slots.
하지만 내 오른손이 슬롯머신을 하라고 했어
Stop it! That's enough!
하지 마! 됐다니까!
Life is so cruel!
인생은 너무 잔인해
Dear God, take me back in time, before I stepped inside to play.
신이시여, 저를 노름하기 전 그 시간으로 데려가 주소서
Please!
제발요!
JASHIN-CHAN LIFE THEATER FIN
'사신짱 인생극장 끝'
Jashin-chan!
사신짱
There you are, my ATM.
내 ATM이 왔구나
I was just on my way to see you.
널 보러 가던 중이야
I brought you Fresh Moon, your favorite.
네가 제일 좋아하는 프레시 문을 가져왔어
Fresh Moon?
프레시 문?
Fresh...?
프레시...?
New...?
새...?
Moon? A new moon?
달? 새 달이라고?
A fresh start.
새로 시작하는 거지
This is my moment.
내 때가 온 거다
When shall I seize it?
기회를 언제 잡지?
Now's the time!
바로 잡아야지!
Are you okay?
너 괜찮아?
I beg you.
부탁한다
Lend me 20,000 yen!
20,000엔을 빌려줘!
I'll double it for you!
내가 두 배로 만들 거야
Sucker!
호구다!
You idiot!
이 멍청이!
You really pushed your luck today.
오늘 정말 운만 믿고 덤비더니
And came out a broke loser.
빈털터리로 돌아왔어
You even had the gall to spend our dinner budget.
뻔뻔하게 우리 저녁 살 돈을 다 써?
I have no choice but to kill you.
널 죽일 수밖에 없지
Medusa, help me!
메두사, 도와줘!
Please forgive her!
제발 용서해!
She's sorry!
미안해하잖아!
She's a good girl by nature.
본성은 착한 아이야
Right, Jashin-chan?
그렇지, 사신짱?
See? Look at that pure smile.
봤지? 저 순수한 미소를 봐
My face...
내 얼굴...
She's corrupt by nature.
쟤는 천성이 타락했어
Are you all right?
괜찮니?
Not at all.
전혀 안 괜찮아
I give you an allowance.
내가 용돈을 주잖아
-Limit yourself to that money. -Okay.
- 그 돈 내에서만 써 - 그래
Make sure you pay Medusa back her 20,000 yen too.
메두사에게 20,000엔도 갚고
TOO BROKE TO PAY BACK
'갚을 돈이 없음'
No excuses.
변명은 안 통한다
Roger that!
알겠습니다!
Don't worry, pay me back when you can.
걱정하지 마, 형편이 될 때 갚아
Quit spoiling her, Medusa.
버릇 잘못 들이지 마, 메두사
The money you blew? It's coming out of your allowance.
네가 날린 돈은 네 용돈에서 나간 거야
Redeem yourself. Go get the groceries this time.
만회해 이번엔 가서 먹을 걸 사 와
You got it!
네!
I won't disappoint you this time!
이번엔 실망하게 하지 않겠습니다!
I promise never to give in to my demons again!
내 안의 악마에게 절대로 굴복하지 않는다고 맹세합니다
Jashin-chan...
사신짱...
Should I go with you?
같이 갈까?
No need.
필요 없어
I reap what I sow.
내가 저지른 일이니 내가 해야 해
Then I will earn her trust back!
그래야 유리네가 날 다시 믿을 거야
That's the spirit!
바로 그거야!
Catch you later!
이따 보자!
Jashin-chan... Where could she be?
사신짱... 어디에 있는 걸까?
What is this?
이건 뭐지?
What a shame.
안타깝군
Japan's supposed to be the country with the 13th-best air quality in the world.
일본은 세계에서 13번째로 가장 공기 질이 좋은 나라라던데
What's taking her so long?
왜 이렇게 늦는 걸까?
Think she...?
혹시 그 애가...?
Let's believe in her. I know she's a good girl.
사신짱을 믿자 좋은 애라는 걸 난 알아
Don't strike out on life with gambling and blow!
노름으로 다 날리고 인생을 망치지 마세요
Jashin-chan dropkick!
사신짱 드롭킥!
In the park!
공원이다!
Thanks for the bread crusts!
빵 껍질 줘서 고맙다!
Later!
또 봐!
I know you get fed!
넌 먹을 게 있으면서
So why steal from me?
왜 내 걸 뺏는 거야?
That was three days' worth of food...
그건 내 3일 치 음식이야...
Oh, Pekola, what a sorry sight.
페코라, 몹시 딱한 광경이군
Poporon.
포포롱
I was ready to crack open that devil's head
저 악마 머리를 깨부숴 열려고 했는데
but she ran off.
쟤가 달아났어
But, wait a minute...
하지만, 잠깐...
Just the other day,
요전 날
the devil came by to drop off curry for Pekola.
페코라에게 카레를 주려고 저 악마가 왔었지
Could it be...
그럼 혹시...
Did you befriend a devil even though you're an angel?
넌 천사인데 악마와 친구가 된 거야?
Seriously?
세상에
Pekola...
페코라...
It's not like that.
그런 게 아니야
We're not friends or anything.
우리는 친구도 뭐도 아니야
What happened to your halo?
네 후광은 어디에 있니?
That devil ate mine.
그 악마가 내 걸 먹었어
Ate it?
먹었다고?
Yum!
맛있다!
Halos are edible?
후광이 먹는 거였어?
Was it good? What did it taste like?
맛있었니? 어떤 맛이야?
The best sauce for it? How's the texture?
가장 어울리는 소스는? 식감은 어때?
How should I know? I'm not the one who ate it.
내가 어떻게 알아? 먹은 사람은 내가 아니야
What would a halo taste like?
후광의 맛은 어떨까?
It must be fluffy like meringue.
머랭처럼 거품이 폭신할 거야
Velvety soft like fish roe.
생선 알처럼 아주 부드럽고
And of course, oh, so sweet
그래, 물론 달콤하겠지
like vanilla ice cream.
바닐라 아이스크림처럼
Wait, does that mean you can't go back to Heaven either?
잠깐, 그럼 너도 천국으로 돌아가지 못하는 거야?
Yup, and I never told anyone I was coming down here.
응, 여기 내려온다고 아무에게도 말 안 했어
I guess I'll just have to wait until it regenerates.
재생할 때까지 기다리는 수밖에 없지
I see...
그렇구나...
Wait, regenerate?
잠깐, 재생한다고?
How did you not know?
어떻게 그걸 모르지?
Our halos regenerate over time.
후광은 시간이 지나면 재생해
Were you really a high-level angel?
너 정말 상급 천사가 맞아?
But there's no way to know how long it will take.
하지만 그 시간이 얼마나 걸릴지는 알 수 없지
Could be days, could be years.
며칠이 될지 몇 년이 될지 몰라
I see.
알겠어
In that case, let's hope someone finds us here.
그렇다면 누군가 우리가 여기 있는 걸 찾길 바라자
We've got no choice but to survive in this world.
우리는 이 세계에서 살아남아야만 해
I guess so.
그런 것 같네
Let's cease fire between us for now
우리 둘 사이의 전쟁은 당분간 멈추는 거야
and work together to survive in the human world!
그리고 이 인간 세계에서 함께 생존하도록 힘을 합치자
You gotta be kidding me.
지금 농담하니?
I don't need your help for anything.
네 도움은 하나도 필요 없어
Plus, you're too naive.
게다가 넌 너무 순진해
You'll only be a burden when it comes to survival.
생존하는 데 결국 짐만 될 거야
So that's that. I'd much rather be a lone wolf.
얘기 끝났어 오히려 혼자가 훨씬 낫지
On that note, I'll take my leave.
그럼, 난 간다
Thought this was a halo? Fooled you!
이게 후광이라고 생각했죠? 속은 겁니다
It's a baumkuchen.
바움쿠헨이죠
Is Poporon really going to be okay by herself?
포포롱이 혼자서 정말 괜찮을까?
Today, Japan ranks at 40th in the world as the best place to live,
오늘날 일본은 세계에서 가장 살기 좋은 곳이자
and where foreigners want to live.
외국인이 선호하는 나라 중 40위다
Fifty-first for its happiness level.
행복 수준은 51위
Number three as the devil's most desired place to live.
악마가 가장 살기 원하는 곳으론 3위고
And it's ranked 78 as an angel's most desired place to live.
천사가 가장 살기 원하는 곳으론 78위를 차지한다
I'm so close...
조금만 더 가까이 가면...
A fake coin?
가짜 동전?
Dear God!
신이시여!
Earn 2000 yen per hour by cleaning people's ears on your lap.
사람을 무릎에 눕혀놓고 귀 청소를 해 주면 시간당 2,000엔을 벌어
It's so easy!
너무 쉬워!
Sounds fair to me.
괜찮은 것 같다
I'm in!
난 할래!
Earn 50,000 yen by taking pills on a schedule, in this building, for a month!
이 건물에서 한 달 동안 정한 대로 약을 먹으면 50,000엔을 벌지
With that kind of money,
그 돈이면
I could buy 71 copies of 4K Ultra HD Blu-ray discs.
4K 울트라 HD 블루 레이 디스크를 71개나 살 수 있어
Just by selling handshake event tickets!
악수 행사 티켓을 파는 것만으로!
Prey on wealthy-looking otaku and get them to buy art, easy!
부자처럼 보이는 오타쿠를 노려서 그림을 사게 하는 거야, 쉬워!
You'd get a good cut.
당신 몫은 잘 받겠어
A pretty girl like you would make a killing! You in?
아가씨처럼 예쁜 여자는 끝내줄 텐데 일을 할래?
I'm really tempted.
마음이 정말 흔들리네
WE WILL BUY DVD - BD ENTRANCE
'매입합니다 DVD, BD, 입구'
MARI SHIRAISHI'S NEW RELEASE!
'마리 시라이시 신작 발표!'
You're out-of-this-world cute, like an angel!
천사처럼 정말 예쁘시군요
I've got a great gig reserved for pretty girls just like you.
당신처럼 예쁜 분을 위해 멋진 일을 준비해 뒀죠
So, what do you say?
어때요?
Really?
정말요?
Good grief.
맙소사
She has no idea what she's getting herself into.
저 애가 지금 무슨 짓을 하는지 전혀 모르는군
She's a bit of a brat, but...
잘난 척하긴 하지만
As an angel, I can't just abandon her.
난 천사야 저 애를 버릴 수는 없어
I gotta convince her to team up with me.
나와 같은 팀이 되도록 설득해야겠다
Plus, a decent employer wouldn't hire anyone without a background check!
더군다나 좋은 고용주라면 배경 조사도 안 하고 아무나 고용하진 않아
Thank you very much.
정말 고맙습니다
That was great.
참 좋았어요
Here's the ramen and fried rice.
라면과 볶음밥 나왔습니다
You're adorable!
예쁘시네요!
Oh, stop it.
별말씀을요
Guess I was wrong.
내가 잘못 생각했군
Drink your mapo tofu!
마파두부는 마셔야지!
-Here. -Thanks!
- 받아 - 고마워
Peanuts.
땅콩이네
Ogre's coming.
도깨비가 오고 있어
Ogre?
도깨비?
I summoned him from Hell for Setsubun, the spring ritual.
세츠분 봄 의식을 하려고 지옥에서 내가 불렀어
You guys celebrate Setsubun in Hell too?
지옥에서도 세츠분을 기념하니?
We sure do!
당연히 하지!
At the end, you eat the same number of beans as your age.
마지막엔 자기 나이와 같은 수의 콩을 먹어
That's easier said than done!
말은 쉽지만 몹시 어려운 일이야
Give me water!
물 줘!
I can't eat anymore...
난 더 못 먹어...
That's just like Japan.
일본하고 똑같네
Ogre should be here by now.
도깨비가 이미 와야 했는데
Yurine, when he shows up, throw the peanuts at him so he doesn't come in.
유리네, 도깨비가 오면 땅콩을 던져서 못 들어오게 해
We'll be blessed with luck all year,
우리는 올해 내내 복 받을 거야
with victory after victory on the slots-- Finally!
슬롯머신으로 따로 또 따고... 왔다!
I'm sorry. Please accept my apologies for my tardiness.
미안해요, 제가 늦었어요 사과드릴게요
There's no excuse for tardiness, damn Ogre!
늦은 주제에 무슨 핑계야 이 도깨비야!
Devils out! Fortune in!
악마는 가라! 복은 들어와!
Enough!
그만해
How could you be so cruel to something so cute?
이렇게 귀여운 애에게 넌 너무 잔인해
But this is my job, miss.
하지만 이게 제 일입니다 아가씨
Dummy!
멍청이!
Don't bring him inside!
그걸 안에 들이면 안 돼
It'll ward away our fortune!
그것 때문에 복이 달아난다고!
Great, another penniless year.
잘한다, 또 돈 없이 한 해를 보내겠군
You're the one who wards off the fortune.
복을 쫓는 건 바로 너지
I got scolded because of you!
너 때문에 내가 혼났어
Like I said...
말했듯이
Jashin-chan...
사신짱
If you bully him again, I'll trim your meat
또 이 애를 괴롭히면 케밥 나이프로
bit by bit with a kebab knife.
네 고기를 잘게 잘라내 주지
Stop! Please! I beg you!
하지 마, 제발! 내가 빌게
I'm sorry. I'll stop bullying.
미안해, 괴롭히지 않을게
Good. Let's go back to the ritual, shall we?
좋아, 이제 다시 의식을 진행해 볼까?
Ready?
준비됐어?
But not with the little guy again.
또 이 작은 애랑 하는 건 아니지?
Hold him for a sec.
잠깐만 들어줘
What's that?
그건 뭐지?
A specialized bean gun.
특수한 콩 총
No!
안 돼!
Devils out!
악마는 가라!
Boy, that felt great.
기분이 매우 좋군
I feel that fortune coming in.
복이 들어오는 느낌이야
Minos took responsibility and ate all the peanuts thrown.
미노스는 책임을 지고 떨어진 땅콩을 모두 먹었습니다
What? Fine. I'll eat it all-- All?
뭐? 그래 내가 다 먹을게, 전부... 전부?
Damn Ogre!
못된 도깨비!
Has no respect for high-class devils!
상급 악마에 대한 존경심이 없어
Thanks to Yurine, the Setsubun ritual was a bust.
유리네 덕에 세츠분 의식이 엉망이 됐어
So annoying.
정말 짜증 난다
Now I gotta find someone weaker to bully.
이제 더 약한 애를 찾아서 괴롭혀야겠다
Fresh and delicious!
신선하고 맛있습니다
The stores are pushing ehomaki as a seasonal item,
가게들이 계절 품목으로 에호마키를 홍보합니다
but it hasn't caught on yet.
하지만 아직 유행은 아닙니다
They even sell ehomaki-style roll cakes and push them as sweet ehomaki.
에호마키식 롤 케이크를 팔면서 달콤한 에호마키라고 선전하지만
But that hasn't caught on at all.
인기는 전혀 없죠
The future of ehomaki looks gloomy!
에호마키의 미래는 암울합니다
It's freezing.
너무 춥다
Physical labor every day
육체노동을 매일 해서
is taxing on the body and mind.
몸과 마음이 점점 지쳐간다
And I barely make any money.
돈도 거의 못 벌고
What has become of this country?
이 나라는 왜 이렇게 된 거지?
This is why Japan ranks second as the country where people get the least amount of sleep.
이래서 일본이 사람들이 가장 적게 잠자는 나라로 2등인 거야
People here take the least paid leave too.
여기 사람은 유급 휴가도 제일 적게 가지
It ranks 114 in countries without gender gaps.
성차별 없는 국가로는 114위고
Second as the devil's most desired place to live.
악마가 가장 살기 원하는 곳으론 2위야
While it's 145 as an angel's most desired place to live.
천사가 가장 살기 원하는 곳으론 145위인데 말이지
Devils out.
악마는 가라
Angels die.
천사는 죽어라
Hey, quit that!
얘, 하지 마!
Did this pest really have to show up now?
이 귀찮은 애는 꼭 지금 나타나야 하나?
Don't let food go to waste.
음식을 버리면 안 돼
That's not like you.
너 같지 않다
WASTE LIVES NOT FOOD.
'목숨은 버려도 음식은 버리면 안 된다'
Yup, that's my philosophy!
그래, 그게 내 철학이지!
It's still perfectly edible.
이건 충분히 먹을 수 있어
Forget the three-second rule, I go by the 30-second rule.
3초 룰은 잊어버려 난 30초 룰을 따른다
You're fine.
괜찮아
Just peel off the shell like this, see?
이렇게 껍질을 벗겨, 봤지?
It's good!
맛있다
There's some here.
저기도 몇 개 있다
Over here too!
여기도 있다!
-Take the whole bag. -What?
- 이 봉지를 통째로 받아 - 뭐?
This too.
이것도
-Yurine made me bring it to you. -So long!
- 유리네가 갖다 주라고 했어 - 굉장히 길다
A hand roll?
데마키야?
It's called ehomaki.
에호마키라는 거다
It brings you good fortune if you eat it facing the lucky direction.
복이 오는 방향을 향해 먹으면 네게 복을 가져다줄 거야
This year, you gotta face that way.
올해는 저쪽을 봐야 해
Don't eat it in your cardboard house.
네 박스 집에선 먹지 마
It'll poke out.
튀어나올 거야
I'll have it outside.
밖에서 먹을 거야
I'm done here.
여기 볼일은 끝났으니
I gotta make one for Yurine now.
유리네한테 줄 걸 하나 만들어야지
Thank you.
고마워
-Ehomaki, yum! -Eho...
- 에호마키는 맛있지 - 에호...
That way, right?
저쪽이라고 했지?
All right, here I go.
좋아, 시작한다
Fortune, come to me...
복아, 내게로 와...
30-second rule!
30초 룰!
Delicious! I can already feel the good fortune coming.
맛있다! 벌써 복이 내게 오는 게 느껴져
She just ate food from the ground!
저 여자가 땅에 떨어진 음식을 먹었어요
Now she's choking on it!
지금은 목이 막혔어요
Watch and learn.
보고 배워
Come on, even I know not to eat food off the ground.
저런, 나도 땅에 떨어진 음식은 먹으면 안 되는 걸 알아요
Wait, was I just on my way to Heaven?
잠깐, 방금 내가 천국에 가던 중이었나?
Am I imagining things?
내 상상일까?
Good fortune, where are you?
복아, 넌 어디에 있니?
Too cute!
귀엽다!
You used Medusa's credit card number
메두사의 신용카드 번호를 써서
and spent 100,000 yen on social-network games?
10만 엔을 SNS 게임에 썼어?
The slots aren't enough for you?
슬롯머신으론 모자랐니?
You tried to borrow even more money yesterday.
어제는 더 많은 돈을 빌리려고 했지
Time to be disappear...
사라질 시간이다
You're not going anywhere.
넌 아무 데도 도망 못 가
Medusa! How could you rat me out like that?
메두사! 네가 날 일러바쳤어?
I was worried you were becoming a game junkie!
네가 게임 중독이 될까 봐 걱정돼서 그랬어
That's none of your business! You act like you're the victim!
그게 너와 무슨 상관인데! 네가 지금 피해자인 척하잖아
Medusa is the victim.
메두사가 피해자다
Why would you give her your card number?
넌 왜 쟤에게 카드 번호를 준 거야?
It wasn't my PIN so I thought it was okay.
비밀번호가 아니라서 괜찮을 줄 알았어
Be more cautious.
더 조심해
Hey, don't bully Medusa.
어이, 메두사는 괴롭히지 마
You know you're only enabling her bad habits.
네가 쟤 나쁜 버릇을 더 부추기는 걸 아니?
Get a new card as soon as you get back to Hell.
지옥으로 가자마자 새 카드를 만들어
Okay.
알겠어
Oh, Jesus.
맙소사
You always get Medusa involved in your mess.
항상 네가 일을 저지르곤 메두사를 끌어들이는구나
I'll pay her back eventually.
언젠가는 내가 다 갚을 거야
How can you without a job?
일도 안 하면서 어떻게 갚지?
Sell clothes I don't wear.
안 입는 옷을 판다
Sold!
팔렸다!
Borrow more from Medusa to bet on horses?
메두사에게서 돈을 더 빌려서 경마 게임에 걸까?
Go! Go! Pass that horse!
달려, 달리라고! 저 말을 추월해!
Or else you'd better run for your life!
아니면 필사적으로 도망치는 게 좋을 거다!
Why don't you have any ambition to go out and work for your money?
왜 밖에 나가서 직접 일해서 돈 벌 생각을 안 하지?
You don't even have clothes.
넌 옷도 없잖아
You hopeless...
이 구제 불능...
A game notification!
게임 알림이다
Did I fully recover?
완전히 회복된 건가?
Don't you dare look at your phone while I'm talking to you.
내가 말하는데 감히 휴대폰을 보면 안 되지
No! My poor finger!
안 돼! 내 불쌍한 손가락!
No sign of remorse whatsoever.
전혀 반성하는 기미가 없어
Are you okay?
괜찮니?
My hand... It hurts...
내 손이... 아파
It'll regenerate eventually.
재생할 거다
I won't last any longer.
난 얼마 못 살아
Don't give up, Jashin-chan!
포기하지 마, 사신짱!
-I have one last wish... -What is it?
- 마지막 소원이 있어 - 그게 뭔데?
You have two credit cards, right?
넌 신용카드가 두 개지?
I do.
응
Text me your other card number...
문자로 네 다른 카드 번호를 알려줘
You never learn.
정말 버릇을 못 고치는군
No, not the chainsaw!
안 돼, 전기톱은 안 돼!
That's enough.
그만하자
I've had it with you.
나도 네가 질렸어
The end.
끝이다
Where did you send her?
어디로 보낸 거야?
Where am I?
여기가 어디지?
JULY 9TH 17:00
'7월 9일 오후 5시'
It's right before yesterday's sale.
어제 세일 전이네
I still have the 10,000 yen I spent yesterday.
어제 썼던 10,000엔이 아직도 있다
I must have traveled back in time!
과거로 시간여행을 온 거다!
There was a wormhole beneath Yurine's apartment!
유리네 아파트 아래에 웜홀이 있지
Hooray, God answered my prayers!
만세, 신께서 내 기도에 응답하셨다
This must be a test. I shouldn't repeat my mistakes.
이건 시험이야 실수를 반복하면 안 돼
Play... Play...
게임 해... 게임 해...
Or maybe they sent me back here...
아니지, 날 이리 다시 보내서
so I could win this time...
이기라는 건지도 몰라
Yeah, of course I'll win!
그래, 당연히 내가 딸 거야
I'll beat all the odds!
모든 역경을 이겨내고
I'm gonna rewrite history!
내가 역사를 다시 쓸 거야
Watch me, Yurine.
잘 봐라, 유리네
I'll bring home a fancy hot-pot dinner tonight!
오늘 밤 내가 근사한 스키야키 저녁을 가져올 거다
Jashin-chan rewrote history.
사신짱은 역사를 다시 썼죠
She strayed into a never-ending time loop.
끝이 없는 타임루프에서 길을 잃게 됩니다
How many loops will she have gone through
얼마나 많은 루프를 거쳐야
by the time we see her next?
우리가 그녀를 다시 보게 될까요?
We shall meet again once she recognizes her mistake.
사신짱이 실수를 깨달을 때 우리는 다시 만날 겁니다
Though, there's no telling when that might be...
그게 언제가 될지는 알 수 없죠
Dropkick on her, yeah her I'll take you down again
드롭킥을 날린다! 저 애야! 널 다시 무찌를 거다!
Hate you Love doesn't exist in this world
네가 싫어! 이 세상에 사랑이란 없어
Fear the dropkick An angel looks for her halo
드롭킥을 겁내라! 천사는 후광을 찾는다
As she starves to death
굶어 죽어가면서 말이야
It's a love and hate relationship
이건 애증 관계야
Can't leave each other alone
서로를 가만히 두지 않지
Like a galaxy-bursting shooting star
은하에서 터지는 유성처럼
Slowly, slowly, sneak up and die
천천히, 살금살금 몰래 다가가서 죽인다!
Test my heart, don't stop
내 마음을 떠봐 멈추지 말고
Let's go, dream on No matter human, angel or devil
가자! 꿈꿔! 인간이건 천사건 악마건
We're a happy family
우리는 행복한 가족이다 랄랄라
Let me say, I love you
내가 말할게 난 널 사랑해!
When all is said and done
모든 것이 끝나면
I'm home Welcome back, it's hot pot tonight
나 왔어! 어서 와, 오늘 밤은 스키야키다!
Come, gather everyone Let's enjoy this meal
모두 어서 모여! 이 요리를 즐기자!
For another crazy tomorrow
내일은 또 정신없을 거야
What next? What next? In the end, wake up
뭔데? 또 뭐지? 결국 깨어나!
What's wrong, Jashin-chan?
사신짱, 무슨 일이야?
I ran out of content...
내용이 다 떨어졌어
It's okay.
괜찮아
Everyone's happy watching you be your cute self.
모두 네 귀여운 모습 그 자체를 보면서 행복해하는 거야
So come on,
그러니까
show them your bright smile.
네 빛나는 미소를 보여줘
Okay?
알겠지?
Medusa...
메두사...
That's your smile?
그게 네 미소니?
The iron-made container delivered from afar
멀리서 배달된 철 컨테이너는
was an iron maiden of Elizabeth Báthory.
엘리자베스 바토리가 만든 아이언 메이든이다
And now, it embraces the devils.
이제 그건 악마를 감싼다
Dropkick on My Devil!
사신짱 드롭킥!
We'll dragon-screw into your heart in the next episode too!
다음 화에서도 여러분 마음에 드래곤 스크류를 겁니다